Finding Aid for D.C. Allen House of David Collection, 1795-1980
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Publications
  - Publications by and about James Jezreel (Sixth messenger) (New and Latter House of Israel)
    - A collection of hymns compiled for use at the public meetings of the New and Latter House of Israel. New ed considerably enlarged (London: Trustees of the New and Latter House of Israel n.d. ) 183 p. (Volume FA 25 J59 C697)
    - The destiny of body, soul, and spirit. Tract no. 4 (London: New & Latter House of Israel Book Depot 19--? ]) 8 p. (Box 5)
    - Extracts from the flying roll. Being a series of sermons compiled for the gentile churches of all sects and denominations, and addressed to the lost tribes of the house of Israel / by James J. Jezreel. (Box 5)
      - Sermon 1 (Jerusalem: s.n. 1879 ) 208 p., 2 copies (Volume FA 25 J59 E95 1879)
      - Sermon 2 (Jerusalem: s.n. 1879 ) 268 p. (Volume FA 25 J59 E96)
      - Sermon 3 (Jerusalem: s.n. 1881 ) 249 p., 2 copies (Volume FA 25 J59 E97)
    - Extracts from the flying roll. Being a series of sermons compiled for the gentile churches of all sects and denominations, and addressed to the lost tribes of the house of Israel. Sermon 1 / by James J. Jezreel. (Jerusalem: s.n. 1879 reprinted Maidstone, Kent: Printway, 1970 ) 208 p. (Volume FA 25 J59 E95 1970)
    - Extracts from the flying roll: being a series of sermons compiled for the gentile churches of all sects and denominations, and addressed to the lost tribes of the house of Israel. Sermon 1, part 1 (Jerusalem: s.n. 1879 c 1881 ) 25 p. (Box 5)
    - Extracts from the flying roll. Being a series of sermons compiled for the gentile churches of all sects and denominations, and addressed to the lost tribes of the house of Israel. Volume 1 /by J.J.J. (Jerusalem: s.n. 1881 ) 208, 268, 249 p. (Volume FA 25 J59 E98)
    - Foundations for our faith: being reasons for the belief held by "The New and Latter House of Israel." Tract no. 7 ([S.l.: s.n. 189-? ]) 12 p. (Box 5)
    - Has prophecy ceased? Tract no. 6 (London: New & Latter House of Israel Book Depot 19--? ]) 8 p. (Box 5)
    - The hope of Israel's twelve tribes. Tract no. 8 ([S.l.: s.n. 19--? ]) 16 p. (Box 5)
    - Is the law of Moses abolished? Tract no. 2 (London: New & Latter House of Israel Book Depot 19--? ]) 8 p. (Box 5)
    - The pioneer of wisdom: a weekly newspaper devoted to the ingathering and restoration of Israel. Vol. 3 ( 1890 ) (Volume FA 25 J59 P662)
    - What is immortality? Tract no. 5 (London: New & Latter House of Israel Book Depot 19--? ]) 7 p. (Box 5)
    - Will any soul suffer eternal pain? (London: New & Latter House of Israel Book Depot 19--? ]) 8 p. (Box 5)
  - Publications by and about Helen Barltrop (The Panacea Society)
    - The panacea (Bedford, England: Panacea Society) (Box 5)
      - Vol. 8 ( 1931/1932 ) 288 p. (Volume FA 25 B258 P187)
      - Vol. 9 ( 1932/1933 ) 288 p. (Volume FA 25 B258 P188)
  - Publications about British-Israelism
    - Anglo-Israel; or, the Anglo-Saxon nation identified with the lost tribes of Israel / by Rev. W. H. Poole (New York: James Huggins, printer and publisher, [ 1880 ? ]) 80 p. (Box 5)
    - The Anglo-Saxon nation or Is Great Britain Israel? / by L. Sale-Harrison (Philadelphia, Pa.: L. Sale-Harrison, c 1928 ) 29 p. (Box 5)
    - The Anglo-Saxon riddle: or, The riddle of our Israelitish origin, present grandeur, and future greatness / by Antiquary, a clergyman of the Church of England. Also, Its solution / by Edward Hine. Rev. and reprinted by H.J.H. (New York: James Huggins, printer and publisher 1878 ) p. 282-296 (Box 5)
    - The delusion of British-Israelism: a comprehensive treatise / by Anton Darms (New York: Loizeaux Brothers, Bible Truth Depot n.d. ) 224 p. (Volume FA 25 D222 D366)
    - The focus of history. Sacred and secular. Facts of iron. The times and seasons of Rome / by Charles A.L. Totten. Part 1. Our race, series 4, no. 14 (New Haven, Conn.: Our Race Pub. Co. 1894 ) 264 p. (Volume FA 25 T719 F652)
    - The Israel promises and their fulfillment: an examination of the pronouncements found in the book entitled "The hope of Israel: What is it?" / by Samuel Hinds Wilkinson (London: John Bale, Sons & Danielsson 1936 ) 195 p. (Volume FA 25 W687 I85)
    - The lost ten tribes / by Rev. Joseph Wild, DD (Boston: A.A. Beauchamp 1919 ) 96 p. (Volume FA 25 W668 L881)
    - Manasseh and United States, an essay, delivered by the Rev. Joseph Wild, D.D., in Union Congregational Church, Brooklyn, N.Y. before the Lost Israel Identification Society. 2nd ed., rev. and ill. (New York: James Huggins 1879 ) 16 p. (Box 5)
    - Our inheritance in the great seal of "Manasseh," the United States of America. Its history and heraldry; ant its signification unto "the great people" thus sealed / by Charles A.L. Totten. The seal of history, vol. 2. Our race, series 5, no. 19 (New Haven, Conn.: Our Race Pub. Co. 1897 ) 380 p. (Volume FA 25 T719 O93)
    - A rÃ?Â©sumÃ?Â© of the scriptural argument proving the identity of the Anglo-Saxons with the lost ten tribes of Israel / by Philo-Israel. Reprinted, with additions and corrections, from Israel in Britain, by J. Huggins. New and enl. ed. (New York: James Huggins 1880 ) 8 p. (Box 5)
    - The United States and the British Commonwealth in prophecy / by Herbert W. Armstrong (Pasadena, Calif.: Radio Church of God, c 1954 ) 26 p. (Box 5)
  - Publications by and about Richard W. Hill (follower and interpreter of Benjamin Purnell)
    - Bible questions and answers made plain. No. 2, The little book open (Mt. Gilead, N.C.: R.W. Hill 1956 ) 129 p. (Box 5)
    - The flying message. No. 2, Life (Mt. Gilead, N.C.: Richard Walter Hill 1949 ) 28 p. (Box 5)
    - Light, life and immortality ([Mt. Gilead, N.C.?: R.W. Hill?] 1960 ) 51 p. (Box 5)
    - The little book of life and redemption. No. 1 / Richard W. Hill (Charlotte, N.C.: Printed by Standard Printing Co., c 1946 ) 91 p., 2 volumes (Box 5)
      (Allen annotation: Printed by offset lithography. There is another issue printed from the same plates but with different wraps and of slightly larger format.)
    - Seven seals of truth. Vol. 1 (Mt. Gilead, N.C.: Mary Rose Hill 1954 ) 82 p. (Box 5)
      (Allen annotation: Wraps printed from type. Text mimeographed. Apparently only one volume printed.)
    - The seven seals unloosed: a series of twelve volumes, compiled for the twelve tribes of Israel scattered abroad, the remnant to be gathered from among both Jew and Gentile of all sects and denominations / by Richard Walter Hill (S.l.: Richard Walter Hill 1945- )
      (Allen annotation: It has not been possible to determine if the proposed 12 volumes were actually printed. At present only 3 volumes have been located.)
      - Vol. 1 c 1945 ) 173 p. (Box 5)
      - Vol. 2 c 1947 ) 155 p. (Box 5)
      - Vol. 3 c 1947 ) 157 p. (Box 5)
    - The spirit of the word. Number 1 (Mt. Gilead, N.C.: Mary Rose Hill 1937 ) 105 p. (Box 5)
    - The spirit of truth ([Mt. Gilead, N.C.?: R.W. Hill?] 1958-1963 ) 8 v.
      BHL has 3 volumes only
      - Vol. 1 ( 1958 ) 100 p. (Box 5)
      - Vol. 4 ( 1960 ) 101 p. (Box 5)
      - Vol. 6 ( 1961 ) 100 p. (Box 5)
    - The voice of the seven thunders (Mt. Gilead, N.C.: R.W. Hill 1959 ) 81 p. (Box 5)
  - Esoteric and other writings of uncertain connection with the House of David or Southcottian prophets
    - The Babylonian story of the Deluge and the Epic of Gilgamesh: with an account of the royal libraries of Ninevah ([London]: British Museum 1920 ) 57 p. (Box 5)
    - The biochemic system of medicine: comprising the theory, pathological action, therapeutical application, material medica, and repertory of the twelve biochemic remedies. Based on the discoveries of Dr. W.H. Schuessler / by George W. Carey, M.D. Edited by Edward L. Perry, A.B., M.D. 25th ed. (St. Louis, Mo.: Luyties Pharmacal Co. 1930 ) 535 p. (Volume FA 25 C273 B615)
    - The book of Jasher. 1st ed. (Philadelphia: Bible Corp. of America 1954 ) 267 p. (Volume FA 25 B724 J39)
    - The coming struggle among the nations of the Earth: or, The political events of the next fifteen years described in accordance with prophecies in Ezekiel, Daniel, and the Apocalypse. Showing also the important position Britain and America will occupy during and at the end of, the awful conflict.. Author's American ed. greatly enlarged (New York: George Taylor 1853 ) 40 p. (Box 5)
    - The history and religion of the Samaritans / Priest Amran Ishak, president of the Higher Community of the Samaritan Religion (Jerusalem: Greek Convent Press 19-? ) 37 p. (Box 5)
    - The "I Am" discourses / by the Ascended Master Saint Germain. 2nd ed. (Chicago: Saint Germain Press, c 1936 ) 361 p. (Volume FA 25 S139 I11)
      (Allen annotation to Book of heaven: During the mid-thirties Mary and a number of the membership were, for a time engrossed with Guy Ballard's teachings of St. Germain--the Mighty I Am. In the Book of heaven Mary skillfully incorporates small portions of this foreign doctrine into the Israelite faith apparently in answer to charges of fraud brought by two former members that she had at first adopted Ballard's teachings and recommended them to the membership but repudiated them when she discovered that adherence to Ballard's teachings would subvert her authority over the members.)
    - In Assyrian tents: the story of the strange adventures of Uriel (Philadelphia: Jewish Publication Society of America 1929 ) 248 p. (Volume FA 25 P398 I35)
    - The internal uncleanliness of Man. Lessons 3 and 4, The diagnosis of your diseas and the "Magic mirror." Lesson 5, The secret of vitality. Lessons 15 and 16, The transition diet / by Prof. Arnold Ehret (Butler, N.J.: Dr. Benedict Lust, c 1922 ) 28 p. (Box 5)
    - Physical exercises (S.l.: ArneGrundstrom, c 1939 ) (Box 5)
      (BHL has incomplete copy, including table of contents and sections 1 and 2 of 8.)
    - The physiological basis of singing (S.l.: ArneGrundstrom, c 1939 ) 2 p. (Box 5)
    - Prof. Arnold Ehret's mucusless-diet healing system / by Prof. Arnold Ehret. 5th ed. (Los Angeles: Ehret Literature Pub. Co., c 1924 ) 194 p. Alternate title: A scientific method of eating your way to health. (Volume FA 25 E33 P964)
    - The sixth and seventh books of Moses. The mystery of all mysteries. The citation on all spirits, the spirit in the burning bush, "Helmet of Moses and Aaron," healing by amulets. The wonderful magical and spirit arts of Moses and Aaron, and the old wise Hebrews, taken from the Mosaic books of the Cabala and the Talmud, for the good of mankind / prepared for publication under the editorship of Dr. L.W. de Laurence (Chicago: de Laurence, Scott 1910 ) 190 p. (Volume FA 25 D342 S625)
    - A text-book on prophecy / by Rev. James M. Gray, D.D. (New York: Fleming H. Revell, c 1918 ) 215 p. (Volume FA 25 G779 T355)
    - The two Babylons, or, The papal worship proved to be the worship of Nimrod and his wife / by the late Rev. Alexander Hislop (London: S.W. Partridge 1921 ) 330 p. (Volume FA 25 H673 T974)
    - The Urantia book (Chicago: Urantia Foundation 1955 ) 2097 p. (Volume FA 25 U72 B724)
    - The word of God. To the faithful of all my reformed churches in the world. The apostles' creed; or, Your belief (London: Published for Shiloh 1799 ) 50 p.
  - Newspapers published by the House of David
    - Shiloh's messenger of wisdom (Benton Harbor, Mich.: House of David, 1st year of the new creation [ 1903 ]-) (Box 5)
      (See catalog record for complete holdings)
      (Allen annotation: The official monthly organ of the House of David began publication December 1903 "14th day of the 8th month, 1st year of the New Creation." The print shop burned after issuing vol. 5, no. 1. Printing of the paper was not resumed until May 1908 and a second printing of vol. 5, no. 1 was issued and the dating made to coincide with May as the first month of the Israelite New Creation calendar.)
      - Volumes 1-18 1903-1922
        (shelved with newspaper collection at NB B478 S556)
      - Volumes 19-45 1922-1949 (Box 6)
      - Volumes 46-66 1949-1970 (Box 7)
      - Volumes 67-77 1970-1979 (Box 8)
  - Newspapers published by the Mary's City of David
    - The New Shiloh messenger: The star of Bethlehem: Mother's book (Benton Harbor, Mich.: Israelite House of David as re-organized by Mary Purnell 1930- )
      (Allen annotation: The monthly organ of the Israelite House of David as re-organized by Mary Purnell. Publication began in April 1930. A volume consists of seventy issues. According to the Israelite's computation of time there are seventy years in one hour of the Lord's time which May account for the deviation from normal publishing practices.)
      - 1930-1941 (Box 9)
      - 1942-1954 (Box 10)
      - 1955-1964 (Box 11)
      - 1965-1972 (Box 12)
      - 1973-1980 (Box 13)
    - Duplicate newspapers (Box 14)
      (some also in newspaper collection at NB B478 S556)
- Manuscript Materials 1904-1980
  The Manuscripts series is small and represents but a fragment of the papers and records that once might have been maintained by the people of the colony relating to their beliefs and to their business activities. Of greatest interest perhaps are those documents (briefs, testimony, and transcripts) relating to the various legal suits against Benjamin Purnell and the Israelite House of David in the 1920s. There is also fragmentary correspondence, some of which relates to the scheduling of the traveling House of David baseball team. This portion of the collection also includes clippings and other written materials about the colony, and miscellaneous items, such as calendars, business forms, menus, programs, and related items, which provide a sense of the economic enterprises of the colony.
  - Background/Biographical
    - "A Bibliographical Sketch of Benjamin and Mary Purnell and the Israelite House of David of Benton Harbor Michigan" (Box 15)
    - Ada Jefferies mss chronology of the House of David colony 1906-1926 (Box 15)
    - Certificate of death -- Mary Purnell (Box 15)
    - Blatz News-Bulletin, vol. 3, no. 7 1936 (Box 15)
      (with article about House of David)
    - House of David history by Raymond F. Hogeboom 1973 entitled, "Israelites v. Gentiles: Benjamin Purnell, the Seventh Messenger of the House of David, Their Legal Contentions within the State of Michigan" (Box 15)
    - Newspaper clippings, 4 folders (Box 15)
    - Index to newspaper articles about House of David 1914-1927 (Box 15)
      (see microfilm of scrapbooks)
  - Administrative Papers
    - Agreement: Israelite House of David as Re-organized by Mary Purnell 1930, photocopy (Box 15)
    - Agreements (Box 15)
      (include agreement between Carrie Daniels Tyndall and House of David, 1931 and agreement for services form, ca. 1935)
    - Broadsides, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Business and outreach activities
      - Advertising brochures and related, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Art Productions catalogs (Box 15)
      - Baseball team score card and other miscellaneous (Box 15)
      - Calendars (Box 15)
        (in oversize box 24)
      - Financial statements (Box 15)
      - Menus (Box 15)
        (for vegetarian restaurant and for park restaurant)
      - Oil and Gas Consumption monthly reports (Box 15)
      - Order blanks 1950-1967 (Box 15)
        (monthly expenditures)
      - Order forms, envelopes, etc. (with House of David printed on them) (Box 15)
      - Permits giving permission to preach on the streets of Wilmington and Greensboro, North Carolina and New Orleans, LA 1920-1921 (Box 15)
      - Price Lists (Box 15)
      - Square dance price schedule (Box 15)
    - By-laws (Box 15)
      (include Amended by-laws of the Israelite House of David, a voluntary religious association (1922); Amendments to by-laws of the Israelite House of David, a voluntary association, unincorporated (1929); Articles of faith and by-laws of the Israelite House of David (Undated, 2 copies); "Agreement To Associate Together as, and Articles of the Religious Faith ... and By-laws ...", Benton Harbor, Michigan (1963))
    - Correspondence 1904-1968 scattered, 6 folders (Box 15)
      (much of the correspondence for the period 1928-1929 relates to the scheduling of the House of David baseball team)
    - House of David mailing list 1949 (Box 15)
    - House of David membership list (Box 15)
    - House of David telephone numbers (Box 15)
    - Official Board of the Israelite House of David
      - Pamphlet: Minutes of the Meeting of the Official Board of the Israelite House of David ... September 26, 1929 (Box 15)
      - Pamphlet: Resolutions Passed at a Meeting of the Official Board of the Israelite House of David ... and Acceptances by Trustees September 26, 1929 (Box 15)
  - Litigation
    - 1921/1923 Berrien County Circuit Court
      - Isabella Pritchard vs. Benjamin Purnell, Mary Purnell (Box 16)
        - Photocopies of court documents (Box 16)
    - 1924 US Supreme Court
      - Benjamin Franklin Purnell, Mary Purnell and His Wife, and the Israelite House of David, A voluntary association vs. John W. Hansel and Margaret Hansel, his wife 1924 (Box 16)
        (petition for certiorari)
    - 1926/1927 Berrien County Circuit Court
      - People of the State of Michigan vs. Benjamin Purnell
        - Photocopies of depositions and testimony, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - 1927 Berrien County Circuit Court
      - People of the State of Michigan, Ex Rel., Andrew B. Dougherty, Attorney General vs. The Israelite House of David, a voluntary association et al.
        - Opinion of the Court (Box 16)
        - Answer of defendants (Box 16)
        - Brief for the plaintiffs, original and photocopy (Box 16)
        - Testimony of Benjamin (including Benjamin's manuscript notes) Given in Open Court in the Trial of the State of Michigan vs. House of David (Benton Harbor, 1928) (Box 16)
        - Transcript of testimony volumes 16, 23, 30, 50, 51 (Box 16)
          (in two expandable folders)
        - Subpoena to Mirriam Croft McFarland to appear in court 1927 (Box 16)
        - Photocopies of correspondence and other papers relating to consequences of court decision (Box 16)
    - 1928/1929 ? Michigan Supreme Court
      - People of the State of Michigan, Ex Rel, Andrew B. Dougherty, Attorney General vs. Israelite House of David, a voluntary association, Benjamin F. Purnell and Mary Purnell
        - Brief for plaintiff and appellee, original and photocopy (Box 16)
        - Brief for defendants and appellants (Box 16)
        - Motion for re-hearing (Box 16)
        - Objection to the motion for rehearing and brief in opposition to motion for rehearing, 2 copies (Box 16)
        - Decree of the Supreme Court (Box 16)
    - 1930 Berrien County Circuit Court
      - William Connon vs. Mary Purnell ... and Israelite House of David as Re-organized by Mary Purnell
        - Photocopies of court documents and correspondence (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous legal (Box 16)
  - Scrapbooks, microfilm
    - Index to newspaper articles concerning the House of David 1914-1927, 4 volumes; 84 pages (Reel 1)
    - Scrapbook 1922-1927 (Reel 1)
    - Scrapbook 1 December 8, 1921-March 21, 1923 (Reel 1)
    - Scrapbook 2 March 21-April 8, 1923 (Reel 1)
    - Scrapbook 3 April 9-30, 1923 (Reel 1)
    - Scrapbook 4 May 1-18, 1923 (Reel 1)
    - Scrapbook 4 May 1-18, 1923 (cont.) (Reel 2)
    - Scrapbook 5 May 18-July 16, 1923 (Reel 2)
    - Scrapbook 6 July 17, 1923-January 31, 1924 (Reel 2)
    - Scrapbook 7 February 1, 1924-October 9, 1926 (Reel 3)
    - Scrapbook 8 November 17-December 18, 1926 (Reel 3)
    - Scrapbook 9 December 19, 1926-January 30, 1927 (Reel 3)
    - Scrapbook 10 February 1-June 7, 1927 (Reel 3)
    - Scrapbook 11 June 8-July 30, 1927 (Reel 3)
    - Scrapbook 11 (cont.) (Reel 4)
    - Scrapbook 12 August 1-November 22, 1927 (Reel 4)
    - Scrapbook 13 November 26, 1927-September 14, 1928 (Reel 4)
      (date on volume is inaccurate)
    - Scrapbook September 24, 1928-January 21, 1929 (Reel 5)
    - Scrapbook 1905-1915 (not in order) (Reel 5)
    - Scrapbook May 6, 1923 (Reel 5)
    - Scrapbook 1930-1934 (Reel 5)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Allen (D.C.) correspondence relating to H of D publications 1969-1975 (Box 17)
    - Christian Israelite Church (mainly Australia)
      - Catechism lessons and questions, and miscellaneous (Box 17)
      - Newsletter (Box 17)
      - Notes from Our Church Organ 1969-1980, 9 folders (Box 17)
    - Ledger containing notes from different sermons and sacred writings (Box 17)
    - "A Letter from Home" from Mary (Box 17)
      (mimeographed mailing)
    - Notes and notepads, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Poetry (Box 17)
    - Various (Box 17)
    - Sound recordings: Cassette tapes and magnetic tapes (2 in.) of messages, some made by David Knight of the Christian Israelite Church, 8 audiocassettes; 8 tapes (Box 17)
    - Sheet music
      - Various songs used by teachers in the House of David school (Box 18)
        (titles not listed)
- Visual Materials
  Researchers interested in images related to the House of David are advised to begin with Photographs and Post Cards, the most inclusive and most easily physically examined subseries of Visual Materials. Most of the images in the Negatives and Slide subseries are duplicative of images in these first two. Effort has been made to identify those items that are available in this collection only in negative or slide format, so that the researcher may better determine when physically reviewing those items may be useful. Researchers who are interested in additional information about an image, especially dates or names of individuals in the image, will often find that information written on the back of the photographic print or, where available, written in pencil on the negative image.
  - Photographic prints, 1906-1970circa 1906-1940 (Box 19)
    - Buildings
      - Ark (Box 19)
      - Bethlehem, Jerusalem and H.O.D. arch (Box 19)
      - Diamond House (Box 19)
      - Jerusalem interior (Box 19)
      - Miscellaneous and unidentified (Box 19)
      - Shiloh (Box 19)
      - Winter scenes (color prints) (Box 19)
    - Business Enterprises, 4 folders
      - Art studio and products (Box 19)
      - Cold storage building and Benton Harbor fruit market (Box 19)
      - Dairy farm and farm products (Box 19)
      - Eden Springs / House of David Park
        - Automobiles, miniature (Box 19)
        - Aviary & green house (Box 19)
        - Concession stands (Box 19)
        - Entertainment performances (Box 19)
        - Flood 1922 (Box 19)
        - General
          - Early 20th century, 2 envelopes (Box 19)
          - Black and white prints August 1970 (Box 19)
          - Color prints August 1970 (Box 19)
        - Log Cabins (Box 19)
        - Open Air Photo Gallery (Box 19)
        - Swimming pool (Box 19)
        - Trains, miniature (Box 19)
        - Zoo & miniature house (Box 19)
      - Food products and cannery (Box 19)
      - Ice cream parlor (first) (Box 19)
      - Machine shop and foundry (Box 19)
      - Musical instrument making (Box 19)
      - Oldsmobile dealership and shop (Box 19)
      - Printing office (Box 19)
      - Restaurants and staff (Box 19)
      - Souvenir shop and products (Box 19)
      - Streetcar depot ("North Depot") (Box 19)
    - People, 6 folders
      - Administrative workers (Box 19)
      - Baseball team (Box 19)
      - Bell, Chick (of and autographed to) (Box 19)
      - Boxer (Frank Wyland) (Box 19)
      - Celebrations, including wedding supper (Box 19)
      - Children (Box 19)
      - Louis, Joe with H. O. D. members 1936 (Box 19)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Black and white prints, mostly portraits, 8 envelopes (Box 19)
        - Color prints, circa 1970 (Box 19)
      - Musical Groups, 2 envelopes (Box 19)
      - Purnell family
        - Benjamin (Box 19)
          see also oversize box